（中央咖啡厅）
嘿  我们这些人里  你们认为下一个结婚的会是谁
Hey, out of all of us, who do you think will get married next?
大概是摩妮卡和钱德
Probably Monica and Chandler.
嘿  能卖我一包纽宝牌淡烟吗
Hi, could I have a pack of Newport Lights? please?
我们没有卖烟  不过街对面的报摊上有卖
Oh, urn, uh, we don't sell cigarettes, but they have them at the newsstand across the street.
那太好了  谢谢
That'd be great. Thanks.
我的天
Oh, my God.
梅莉莎沃伯顿  我可没什么精神准备
Melissa Worbert. I don't think I have the energy for this.
我的天  瑞瑞葛林
Oh, my God! Ray-Ray Green?
梅莉莎  嘿
Melissa. Hey.
我们过去的7次女生联谊会  你都像失踪了一样
You've been M.I.A for the past seven sorority newsletters.
你到底怎么了
What's up with you?
我们到那边去说吧
Why don't I tell you over here?
我最后一次听说你   是说你要结婚了
So last I heard you were gonna get married.
可怜的瑞瑞
Poor Ray-Ray.
不  不  这很好  我其实一切都挺好的
Oh, no, no. it's-It's good. It's all good.
我现在替罗夫罗兰工作  别说了
I actually work at Ralph Lauren. Shut up!
我才不呢  我是运动男装部的主管
I will not. Heh, heh. I'm the divisional head of men's sportswear.
哦  别再说了  你跟罗夫是朋友吗
Oh, shut up more! Now, are you friends with Ralph?
拜托  你是吗
Oh, please. Ha. Are you?
不是
No.
我们一定要一起吃个饭  你明天晚上做什么
Listen, we have to have dinner. What are you doing tomorrow night?
明天  我不知道  现在你知道了  你要和我吃晚饭
Oh, tomorrow. I don't know. Um--You do now. You're having dinner with me.
别说了
Shut up.
我要走了  看到你真好  瑞瑞
I've gotta go. This has been so great, Ray-Ray.
哦  这儿
Oh, there you are.
打电话给我  这是我的名片
Um, so listen, just call me. Here's my card.
哇  谢谢
Oh, wow, thanks.
你在做房地产  不  那是旧名片
Oh, you're in real estate? Oh, no, heh, that's an old card.
我想离开这个行业去做些
Um, I wanted to get out of that and-and do something where I can really...
可以帮助别人和改变世界的工作
...help people and make a difference.
现在你做什么
Wow. What do you do now?
宴会规划
I'm a party planner.
明天见  好
I'll see you tomorrow. Okay.
嘿  伙计们  看谁回来了  是瑞瑞
Hey guys, look who's back. It's Ray-Ray.
闭嘴  那是我大学的朋友梅莉莎
Shut up that was my friend, Melissa, from college.
她看起来非常非常好玩
She seems really, really fun!
她真的很甜  我们曾经很亲密
She's actually very sweet, and we used to be very close.
等一下  她不是那个和你
Wait a minute. she isn't...She's not the one who you...?
和你什么  和你什么
Who you what? Who you what?
是  哇
Yes. Wow!
哇  喔什么  喔什么  和你什么
Wow-Wow, what? Wow what?! Who you what?
没什么大不了
Oh, it's not a big deal.
她们曾经是情人
They were lovers.
什么  什么
What? What?
不  我们不是情人  那又没什么
No, we weren't. It was nothing.
大四的时候  有一天晚上  我们去参加舞会
It was one night, senior year, and we went to a party...
喝了很多桑格利亚调酒  你知道  最后
...had a lot of sangria, and you know, ended up...
我们接吻了
...kissing for a bit.
我有两任老婆是同性恋了
So that's two of my wives.
老友记  第七季  第20集  同性之吻
Friends  S07E20  The One With Rachel's Big Kiss
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
好  乐队在这儿  酒吧在这儿
Okay, so this is where the band is. And this is where the bar is.
这些大头针上都有人名  瑞秋  你在这里
And all these pins have people's names on them. And Rach, here you are.
哦  哇
Oh, wow!
为什么不给我一杯曼哈顿  把我挪到这里
Why don't we just take me and put me with a Manhattan in my hand...
和可爱的男酒保聊天
...talking to the cute bartender.
这些大头针不是用来玩的  对吧
These pins aren't for playing, are they?
红的是我的客人  蓝色的是你的
Okay, the red ones are my guests, and the blue ones are yours.
真可怜  我只有10个客人
This is so sad. I mean, I only have like 10 pins.
钱德  轻松一点  这又不是比赛
Heh, Chandler, relax. It's not a contest.
不是实力相当的比赛
Certainly not a close one.
大家好  嘿
Hello. Hey.
嘿  瑞秋
Hey, Rash.
别再想了
Stop picturing it!
我想就这样吧  座位都确定了  这就是我们的婚礼
Okay, I think that's it. The seating chart is done. This is our wedding.
他们看上去都很开心  对吧
Wow. They all look like they're having fun  don't they?
我爸妈坐哪里
Hey, so where are my parents gonna be?
看看啊  如果这是婚礼大厅
Let's see, well, if this is the wedding hall, then, um...
你父母会在皇后区的家里
...your parents would be over here at home in Queens.
什么  他们没有被邀请  哦不  这太可怕了  他们会发疯的
What they're not invited? Oh, no, that's terrible! they're gonna be crushed!
为什么他们觉得会被邀请
Why would they think they're invited?
你问倒我了  我不
You got me. I don't...
乔伊   抱歉  我以为父母都会来
Joey! Well, I'm sorry. Look, I thought parents were coming.
你的父母会来  钱德的父母也会来
Y'know? Your parents are coming. Chandler's parents are coming.
罗斯的父母也会来
Ross's parents are coming.
罗斯的父母就是我的父母
Ross's parents are my parents.
看么  父母们都会来
Well-well, see, parents are coming.
我想我们应该邀请他们  算了吧  你就想多增加几根蓝色大头针
Y'know I think we should invite them. Oh please, you just want more blue pins.
这实在太悲惨了
Well, this is just sad.
好吧  好吧  也许我重新安排一下位置可以让他们进来
All right. all right. Maybe I can fit them in if I just do some rearranging.
不过  瑞秋可能真的要坐在吧台了
But uh, Rachel may actually have to sit at the bar.
没有问题
That is not a problem.
也许你可以叫杯桑格利亚调酒  去你的
Maybe you'll order a little sangria. Oh, get out of here!
我们所有的晚礼服都在这儿  随便你喜欢哪一件  都可以便宜给你
So now, these are all the tuxedos that we make and if there's anything that you like, we can make you a deal.
任选一件  但这三件是摩妮卡先核准的
Anything at all. But these are the three that Monica pre-approved.
谢谢你帮我挑晚礼服  瑞秋
Uh, well, thanks a lot for hooking me up Rach.
我希望你作为我的客人出席婚礼
And I want you to know that I want you to attend our wedding as my guest.
我是摩妮卡的伴娘
I'm Monica's maid of honor.
好吧  别想把我钉在你的蓝色大头针上
Okay, don't try to blue-pin me.
那这些呢  怎么样  看起来不错  是不错啊
Well, what's the deal with these? These-these look nice. Oh they are nice.
这些都是帮名人量身打造的  他们穿过后就送回来这儿
We-we custom-make tuxedos for celebrities and then when they're done with them they just send 'em back.
你是指像颁奖典礼之后  有些是
You mean, like, for award shows? Some of them.
这都上过红地毯  被人叫着
You mean these tuxes have been down the red carpet with people yelling, uh...
"你是穿谁的  你看来棒极了"
..."Who are you wearing? You look fabulous!"
亲爱的  我建议你  多看一点ESPN体育频道
Honey, might I suggest watching a little more ESPN...
少看一点八卦娱乐节目
...and a little less E!.
谁穿过这些
Okay. Who wore those?
这是汤姆布罗考(NBC新闻主播)穿过的  不错嘛
Umm, well, let's see uh, this one's Tom Brokaw. Not bad.
这是保罗奥尼尔(美财政部长)穿过的
This one is, uh, Paul O'Neil.
他是谁
Who's that?
他是"洋基队"的球员  真的  多看看ESPN
He plays for the Yankees. Seriously, ESPN.
就算有的时候  开着频道当背景听也好啊
Just once in a while. Have it on in the background.
这件是皮尔斯布鲁斯南穿过的
Ooh, this one was Pierce Brosnan.
皮尔斯布鲁斯南  嗯
Pierce Brosnan? Uh-huh.
真的吗  真的啊
Are you serious? Yeah.
O07?
这是詹姆斯邦德的晚礼服  我一定要穿詹姆斯邦德的晚礼服结婚
This is James Bond's tux? Oh, I have to get married in James Bond's tux.
是很酷的礼服
Ha, ha. It's a pretty cool tux.
不只如此  我会是英格兰最强大的武器
Ah, Oh, it's not just that. I would be England's most powerful weapon.
女王陛下的秘密特务  环游世界的负心人
A jet-setting heartbreaker on Her Majesty's secret service.
有杀人执照  什么都不怕的男人
A man who fears no one, with a license to kill.
摩妮卡会不会让我穿这件呢
Would Monica let me wear this?
我们应该学真正的玩法
We should really learn how to play the real way.
我喜欢我们的玩法
I like our way.
将军
Chess!
走的好  是啊
Nice move. Yeah.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
乔伊  我替罗斯和钱德挑选好了婚礼上用的晚礼服  你需要吗
So Joey I just hooked Ross and Chandler up with some tuxedos for the wedding, Do you need one?
不  我主持婚礼  我不穿晚礼服
No, I'm performing the ceremony. I'm not wearing a tux.
那你打算穿什么  五彩长袍
Well, what are you gonna wear? Multi-colored robes.
也许戴一顶帽子
Ooh, and maybe a hat.
摩妮卡知道吗  我想她不知道
Huh. Does Monica know about this? I don't think so.
你告诉她时我能在场吗
Can I please be there when you tell her?
瑞秋等等  今晚要不要去看电影
Hey, Rach wait! you want to go to a movie tonight?
没办法  我去不了  我要和梅莉莎吃饭
Oh, y'know what? I can't. I have to have dinner with that Melissa girl.
我能跟你去吗
Can I come?
我不会出声  你只会听见我摄影机的声音
I won't even talk! You'll just hear the noise from my video camera.
什么  怎么回事  让我来告诉她吗  能让我来告诉她吗
What? What's going on? Oh good! Can I tell her? Can I tell her?!
你要听真实发生的事  还是听乔伊的下流版本
Do you want to hear what actually happened or Joey's lewd version?
乔伊的  好
Joey's. Okay.
喂  少来
Okay, come on.
大学时我有一个朋友
I had this friend from college...
我犯了一个愚蠢的错误  我告诉乔伊有一次
...and I made the mistake of telling Joey that one time...
她和我接吻了
...she and I, you know, kissed a little bit.
对啊  我相信这当然发生了
Yeah, I'm sure that happened.
真的啊  当然
It did. Sure.
嘿  那就真的发生了
Hey, heh. It happened.
是大四那年  有一次开夏威夷主题派对舞会
Yeah, it was senior year in college. It was after the Sigma Chi luau...
我和梅莉莎喝得大醉
...and Melissa and I got very drunk.
结果我们两个接吻了  足足有好几分钟呢
And we ended up kissing. For several minutes.
也就是在脸颊上轻轻地亲了一下
Which means she had a couple spritzers and a peck on the cheek.
你为什么要剥夺我的幻想呢
Why are you taking this away from me? Ugh.
为什么你就不相信呢
Yeah, why is it so hard for you to believe?
好吧  我不知道你是同性恋
Okay. I just I didn't know that you were a lesbian.
我不是说我是同性恋  我只是说那件事发生了
I'm not saying that I'm a lesbian. I'm just saying that this happened.
我只是觉得很狂野  而你是这么地
Okay, it just seems pretty wild. And you're-You know, so...
乖宝宝
...vanilla.
乖宝宝  我不是乖宝宝  我会做很多疯狂的事
Vanilla? I'm not vanilla. I've done lots of crazy things.
我还喝醉了  在拉斯维加斯还结了婚
I mean, I got drunk and married in Vegas.
和罗斯
To Ross.
这样吧  如果你还不相信
All right, y'know what? If you don't want to believe me  about this...
今晚和我一起去吃饭  她会告诉你
...why don't you just come with me to dinner tonight and she'll tell you.
好吧  反正我也想像不出来
Okay. All right! Yeah! Because I can't picture it.
你该到我脑子里来看看
Oh-ho, you should get inside my head.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
猜猜我为你的婚礼弄到什么了
Guess what I got for your wedding?
一个脑袋上有衣架的畸形女友
A freakishly thin date with a hanger for a head?
不是  瑞秋帮我找一件晚礼服  可不是随随便便的一件
No. Rachel hooked me up with a tux. But not just any tux.
是蝙蝠侠的晚礼服
Batman's tux!
什么  没错
What? That's right.
这件晚礼服是给瓦尔基尔默在电影中用的  让他穿在票房冠军电影里
Made expressly for Val Kilmer, and worn by him in the hit film...
就是他演的那部蝙蝠侠
...that Batman film he was in.
你不能穿那件  我穿了名人的晚礼服
You can't wear that. I'm wearing the famous tux.
詹姆士庞德的晚礼服    那又怎样
James Bond's tux. So?
那又怎样  如果你穿那件  会让我显得不那么特别
So—If you wear that, you'll make mine less special.
你需要什么来让那天特别一点吗
Well, you need something to to make this day special?
喂  你有了最特别的一样
Hello! You have the most special thing of all.
你娶了你最爱的女人
You are marrying the woman you love.
拜托  不要抢走我的锋头嘛  拜托拜托
Please, don't take away my cool thing. Please?! Pretty please?
"拜托拜托"   这可不象007
"Pretty please?" Not very, uh, 007.
这是我的婚礼  如果是你结婚  我不会做任何让你生气的事
Look, it's my wedding day okay? If you were getting married, I'd never do anything to upset you.
我结婚的时候  你和我妹妹上床  那就很007
When I got married you slept with my sister. That was pretty 007.
嘿  嘿  好  你来了
Hey. Hey. Okay, good. You're here.
好  我想出办法来了
All right, I figured it out.
我把这两桌的8个人  加上你父母
I'm gonna take 2 tables of 8, I'm gonna add your parents...
变成3桌6个人
...and I'm gonna turn them into 3 tables of 6. Okay?
我已经通知了办酒席的人  要多做两份  都弄好了
And I called the caterer. I added two extra meals, We are good to go!
很好  不过他们不来了
Yeah. They're not coming.
什么
What?
不知道为什么  他们觉得你是因为我才邀请他们的
Somehow they got the idea that you only invited them because of me.
他们有点觉得自己是多余的
They...feel a little unwanted.
真糟糕  确实那样的  不过还是很糟糕
Oh that's too bad. It's true. But too bad.
要不这样摩妮卡  你可以打电话给我妈  乔伊
Look Mon, if you could just call my mom. Oh, Joey.
拜托  让她知道是你真心希望他们去
Come on. Look just-just tell—let her know that you really want them there.
别忘了  这可是每年都给你送很多很多千层面的女人啊
Let's not forget this is a woman who that has sent you many lasagnas over the years.
不  她哪有
No, she hasn't.
有些没送到你手里也不是她的错啊
Is it her fault that some of them didn't make it to you?
那我该怎么说呢
Well, what am I gonna say?
告诉她请帖搞乱了  不  怪邮局好了
Just uh, Just tell them you mixed up invitations. No, no, no, blame it on the post office.
他们最恨邮局  还有爱尔兰人
They hate the post office. And the Irish.
不过我想你不能怪到他们头上
But I don't think you could blame it on them.
喂  你好  崔比亚尼太太吗  我是摩妮卡盖勒
Hello? Yeah, hi. Uh, Mrs. Tribbiani? Hi, this is Monica Geller.
我想告诉你  钱德跟我希望你们能来参加婚礼
I'm just calling to say that Chandler and I uh, really hope you can make the wedding.
我们很多请帖都没寄到
Yeah, apparently a bunch of invitations that we sent weren't delivered.
我猜又是可恶的邮局搞砸的
Um, I guess there was some screw-up at the damn post office.
就是嘛
Tell me about it.
什么美国邮局  更像是美国遗失局
Yeah, yeah, the U.S. Post Office? No. More like U.S. Lost Office.
难道他们都是爱尔兰人吗
What are they, Irish?
总之呢  他叫艾伦  我们在一起三年了
Anyway, his name's Allen. And we've been going out for three years.
他是我做宴会规划的第一位客户
He was my first client when I became a party planner.
那时他正要为他当时的女朋友  规划一场宴会
He was actually planning a party for his girlfriend at the time.
结果就变成这样
Oh, well. No.
他是雪城大学兄弟会的  哦  太棒了
Ah. He was Theta Beta Pi at Syracuse. Oh! Oh, that's great.
菲比  你参加过女生联谊会吗  当然
Phoebe, were you ever in a sorority? Of course.
我是大腿卫生棉条的成员
Yes. I was a, um, Thigh Mega Tampon.
什么
What one?
我们规模也很大  但后来他们把我们解散了
Yeah, Y'know, we were really huge too. But then they had to shut us down...
因为瑞吉娜佛兰姬基死于酒精中毒
...when Regina Phalangie died of alcohol poisoning.
真是糟糕   一颗老鼠屎就毁了一锅粥
Oh, isn't it a shame when one girl ruins it for the whole bunch?
不管了
Anyway...
醉话说的太多了   我告诉菲比
Speaking of drinking too much, I was, uh, telling Phoebe...
姐妹会开夏威夷派对  很疯的那晚  我们亲吻的事
...about that one crazy night after the Sigma Chi luau where you and I uh, we made out.
什么
What?
记得嘛  我们穿着土著裙子  还有椰子壳比基尼上衣
Remember we-Come on, we had sarongs on and we had coconut bikini tops.
之后我们回到家  继续在那儿疯癫
We went back to the house and got really silly...
然后我们接吻了
...and we made out.
瑞瑞  我不知道你在说什么
Wow, Ray-Ray, I have no idea what you're talking about.
真的吗
Really?
罗斯是蝙蝠侠
Ross is Batman.
他还真会掩护秘密身分  瞒了这么久
Well, he did manage to keep his identity secret for a long time.
瑞秋替罗斯弄到  瓦尔基尔默在蝙蝠侠里穿的晚礼服
Rachel got Ross the tuxedo that Val Kilmer wore in Batman.
蝙蝠侠可比詹姆士庞德酷多了
Batman is so much cooler than James Bond.
你在说什么啊  007有好多新式武器   蝙蝠侠有多功能腰带
What are you talking about?!  007 has all those gadgets. Batman has a utility belt.
007有特制的汽车   蝙蝠侠有蝙蝠车
007 has a fancy car. Batman has the Batmobile.
007有美女相伴  蝙蝠侠只有罗宾
007 gets all the ladies. Heh. Batman has Robin.
我们有ESPN台  对吧
We get ESPN, right?
不如你去穿上007晚礼服   我来给你调一杯马丁尼酒
How about you go put on your 007 tuxedo, and I'll make you a nice martini?
我不喜欢  马丁尼
Actually I don't like martinis.
那有搞笑吸管的摇摇饮料呢  好的
A Yoo-Hoo with a funny straw? Ooh, yum.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
请帖上写晚上6点
Listen, I know the invitation says 6:00...
那是指6点入席  还是6点开始表演
...but does that mean that you want people to get there at 6, or the show is gonna start right at 6?
表演
The show?
对  婚礼  知道了
Right, Right. the wedding. Gotcha.
不过婚礼能不能晚一点开始  我是说  婚礼晚一点进行  行吗
But I mean, it's gonna start a little late right? I mean, weddings start late. Right?
你有参加过我规划的婚礼吗
Have you ever been to one of my weddings?
你看  事情是这样的  那天也是我外甥女的洗礼日
Ah, Well look, the thing is it's the same day as my niece's christening...
我真的希望我父母能准时出席来看我
...and I really want my parents to be there in time to see me.
因为我的角色是在开始部分  演出的其他部分没我什么事
'Cause My part's just in the beginning. I'm not even in the rest of the show-Wedding.
婚礼6点开始
The wedding starts at 6.
好  好  我完全明白了
Okay. Okay, I totally hear you.
这样如何  我可以表演个小节目到他们来
Ooh! How about this? I vamp a little till they get there.
你要 "表演"
Heh. You'll "vamp"?
对啊  就像给观众热热身  问问他们从哪儿来
Yeah, yeah, y'know, like warm up the crowd. Ask 'em where they're from.
因为有乔伊崔比亚尼在  就像同时拥有了一个牧师和一个演员
'Cause In Joey Tribbiani, you get a minister and you get an entertainer.
我是一位 "表演牧师"
I'm a "mini-stainer."
不会比这更好的了  不会比这更棒的
There's no one better. There's no one greater.
你怎么会不记得我们接吻的事
How can you not remember us kissing?
不知道  很多从没发生过的事我不记得了
I don't know. I don't remember a lot of things that never happened.
什么
Wha--
拜托  记得我们在卧室外的走廊  一直笑一直笑吗
Come on! Remember, we were on the sleeping porch? We couldn't stop giggling.
我们戴的椰子壳都撞在一起了
And our coconuts kept knocking together.
哦  乔伊的脑袋该爆炸了
Oh, somewhere Joey's head is exploding.
对吧  听着  抱歉  我不是想让你难堪
Yeah—but come on—Listen, I'm sorry I don't want to make you uncomfortable...
但我告诉菲比那件事  她不相信我
...but I told Phoebe it happened, and she doesn't believe me.
对不起  瑞瑞  如果我认为真有那回事  我会承认的
I'm sorry. Ray-ray. I mean, if I thought it happened, I would say it.
也许我醉睡过去后  你亲了我
Maybe I passed out and you did stuff to me while I was sleeping.
没有
No.
瑞秋  没关系的  不必这样  我相信你
Rachel, It's okay, you don't have to do this. I believe you.
如果你说你吻过梅莉莎  你就是吻过梅莉莎
Okay, if-if you say you kissed Melissa, then you kissed Melissa.
谢谢你  菲比  好
Thank you, Phoebe. Okay.
可是她没有  我知道
But she didn't. I know.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
你到哪儿都带着它
You just carry that around?
是的
Yes.
我发现这可以成为我炫耀的资本
I find it to be something of a conversation piece.
你和  阿甘
Between you and...? Gunther.
我们为什么不一起穿上呢
Hey, hey. Why don't we put them on?
拍一张蝙蝠侠和詹姆士庞德一起的照片
Y'know get a picture of Batman and James Bond, together.
我很乐意  但是我的不合身  裤子小了一点
I would but mine doesn't fit. The pants a little tight.
小了一点  我可以看到里面的两个0和一个7
A little tight? I could see double-oh and seven in those pants.
真糟糕  我还很期待  穿着我们的名人晚礼服一起亮相
Well that stinks. I was looking forward to us wearing our celebrity tuxes together.
你意思是你不打算穿你的了  你开玩笑吗  这可是蝙蝠侠的晚礼服
Well, does that mean that you're not gonna be wearing yours? What are you kidding? It's Batman's tux!
我穿上试试
Let me try it on.
好吧  不过只能试穿上衣  两个O和一个7就不要穿进去了
Okay. But just the jacket. double-oh and seven are not getting in there.
好的
0Kay.
双面通风的舒适型   蝙蝠侠
Holy double-vented comfort, Batman!
这是什么
What's this? Huh?
《真情难舍》首映的请柬
An invitation to the At First Sight premiere?
天啊
Oh, my God.
瓦尔基尔默没有在蝙蝠侠里面穿这个
Val Kilmer didn't wear this in Batman.
他穿这个  演瞎子的那部文艺爱情片首映
He wore it to the premiere of some tooty-fruity lovestory where he was a blind guy.
让我看看
Let me see that.
老天
Oh, man.
你唯一的超能力  就是嗅觉发达
The only super power you have is the slightly heightened sense of smell.
摩妮卡  钱德  可以和你们谈谈吗
Hey. Uh, Monica? Chandler? can I talk to you guys for a second?
算了  我放弃了  你想怎样就怎样吧
All right that's it, I give up. Whatever you want, you can have it.
你要唱歌还是跳舞
You want to sing a song? You wanna do a dance?
你想让你妈妈站在圣坛前大喊种族危机  我都不在乎
You want your mom stand at the altar screaming racial slurs? I don't care.
我只是要谢谢你们  为我父母做的一切  他们很高兴
No! No, I-I just want to thank you guys for what you did for my parents. that was really sweet.
能参与你们最特别的一天
They're so happy to get to be a part of your special day.
不客气  告诉他们  我们很高兴他们会来
Well, your welcome. And tell them we're really glad they're coming.
我会的  给你们看  我婚礼要穿的衣服  是他们替我准备的
Okay. I will. Oh, check out what they got me to wear for the ceremony!
我替你们证婚时这样戴  然后
Huh? I wear it like this when I marry you guys. And then this...
在宴会时这样戴
...is for party time.
那是真的  我告诉你那发生过  好的
It happened. I am telling you it happened. Okay.
很高兴认识你
Hey, Well, it was great meeting you.
还有  瑞秋  我想我不会给你打电话了  因为
And, uh, Rachel? I don't think I'll be calling you because, uh...
你变得好奇怪
...you know, you've gotten weird.
保重  两位
Take care, you guys.
什么  等等  等一下  好  听着
Wha-Wait a minute. No wait a minute! Okay, look.
那天晚上的事是  我这辈子里干的最疯狂的一件事
That night was the one wild thing I've ever done in my entire life.
我不会让你这样轻易就否认
and I'm not gonna let you take that away from me.
如果你不记得那件事  也许你会记得这个
Okay, so if you don't remember that, maybe you'll remember this...
我的天  你爱我
Oh, my God. You love me.
什么  我当然记得我们的吻
What? Of course I remember our kiss.
我每时每刻都在想着
I think about it all the time.
我还能听到  椰子壳碰在一起的声音
I can still hear the coconuts knocking together, I...
我不想告诉你  因为我不觉得  你会回报我的爱  现在你回报
I just didn't want to tell you, because I didn't think that you'd return my love. and now that you have...
喔  喔  喔
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
你看谁突然害羞起来了
Aw! Look who's being suddenly shy.
你一定和我有一样的感觉
You can't tell me you don't feel what I feel.
一定是要发自于内心  才能吻得那么好
Nobody can kiss that good and not mean it.
我只是吻功很好
I-I-I-I'm just…I'm just a good kisser!
别说了
Shut up.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你不必道歉
Oh, you don't have to be sorry.
我在开玩笑
I'm obviously kidding.
我没爱上你  我也没爱上她
I'm not in love with you. I'm not in love with her.
我没听到椰子壳撞在一起的声音
I don't hear coconuts banging together.
我和男友做爱时没幻想你的脸
Yeah, I don't picture your face when I make love to my boyfriend.
我要走了
Anyway, I gotta go.
吻别一下吧
A kiss goodbye?
不要  好吧
No? Okay.
我没想到会是这样
I mean, I had no idea that that was gonna...
这是怎么回事
What the hell was that?
我只是想看看这有什么大不了的
I just wanted to see what all the fuss was about.
然后呢  我尝试过更好的
And? I've had better.
好  我找到一件合身的
All right! I found one that fits.
是啊  人们常说  第23次就会成功
Well, you know what they say? 23rd time's a charm.
看看你  好英俊
Aw! Look at you, all handsome.
谁穿过这件  有关系吗
Whose is it? Oh, does it matter?
唯一重要的是你看来很英俊
All that matters is that you look so handsome.
是谁的  我不想讲
Whose is it? I don't want to say.
拜托  我不在乎  是谁的
Oh, come on, I don't care. Come on! Whose is it?
黛安基顿
Diane Keaton.